Branding specialist, marketing all-rounder & graphic designer

patrickjrwhite@gmail.com whatsapp: 614 0373 4656 ITA mob: 39 331 3572216

Hey, I'm Patrick.

Thanks for taking the time to look at my CV. To introduce myself I've written a short summary of who I am and what you can expect from me, followed by all of the other information you might need.

I'm a curious and creative person. I'm easy to get along with. I love branding, I love design, and I love bringing ideas to life. I have many interests, but I could really talk forever about music, films and football.

I've worked across a wide range of creative fields in both small startups and large organisations, and I know how to get the best out of myself and my team in these environments to produce fantastic work.



Experience

Media Strategy Director BANTA Creative Agency 2020—Present

At BANTA I currently work in a senior role with the founding directors to carry out projects efficiently, and to a high standard. I have been responsible for leading brand strategy, campaign strategy and creative direction alongside many other duties - while also taking a handson role in completing projects. I have managed team workflows and internal comms, produced quotes for clients and budgets across a diverse client portfolio.

Digital Communications Executive SKYCITY Entertainment Group 2018—2020

After being promoted to an executive role, I was given greater responsibility within the broader marketing team at SKYCITY Adelaide and played a key role in the launch of multiple new food and beverage venue brands as part of a major expansion to the business. Additionally I was responsible for the strategy, management and content creation for SKYCITY Adelaide's owned digital channels (10+) including their social media, website content and EDMs. I was also responsible for managing and collaborating with external agencies on various projects.

Digital Communications Coordinator SKYCITY Entertainment Group 2016—2018

I began working at SKYCITY Adelaide as an intern carrying out various tasks to support the marketing team and was quickly offered a full-time role. During my time in this coordinator role I was responsible for managing and creating content for the SKYCITY Adelaide website, social media channels and EDMs. I was also often tasked with copywriting for various external marketing material and assisting the marketing team with various tasks.

Main duties

Copywriting
Photography
Video editing
Brand strategy
Graphic design
Digital marketing
Creative direction
Graphic animation
Marketing strategy

Main duties

Copywriting
Photography
Video editing
Brand strategy
Graphic design
Digital marketing

Main duties

Copywriting
Photography
Video editing
Graphic design
Content creation
Digital marketing

Skills

Adobe InDesign Meta/Google Ads Adobe Premiere Microsoft Office Adobe Illustrator HTML/CSS Adobe Lightroom Blender 3D Adobe Photoshop SparkAR Adobe After Effects Webflow

Education

Bachelor of Marketing & Communication University of South Australia 2013—2016

References

Lachlan Stewart

Lead Designer
BANTA Creative Agency
+33 7 49 52 11 29
WhatsApp: +61 419 774 192
lachlanstewart11@gmail.com

Jessica Sinclair

Digital Marketing Manager SKYCITY Entertainment Group +61 466 260 102 jess.sinclair@skycity.com.au

Nick Babadimas

Marketing Lead University of Adelaide (Former SKYCITY colleague) +61 412 367 025 WhatsApp: +61 412 367 025



